[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What language defines the behavior of a web page?",
    "A": " HTML",
    "B": "CSS",
    "C": "XML",
    "D": "JAVASCRIPT",
    "answer":"JAVASCRIPT"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "To insert a JavaScript into an HTML page, which tag is used?",
    "A": " < script=â€™javaâ€™>",
    "B": " < javascript>",
    "C": "< script>",
    "D": "< js>",
    "answer":"< script>"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the below is used in Java script to insert special characters?",
    "A": "&",
    "B": "(BackSlash)",
    "C": "-",
     "D": "%",
     "answer":"(BackSlash)"
  },
 
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the alternate name for Java script?",
    "A": "LimeScript",
    "B": "Both a and d",
    "C": "ECMScript",
    "D": "ECMAScript ",
    "answer":"ECMAScript"
  },

  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How to append a value to an array of Java Script?",
    "A": "arr[arr.length] = value ",
    "B": "arr[arr.length+1] = new Arrays()",
    "C": "arr[arr.length-1] = value",
    "D": "arr[arr.length*1] = value",
    "answer":"arr[arr.length] = value "
  },
  
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
    "A": "var txt = new Array(1:'arr',2:'kimm',3:'jimm')",
    "B": "var txt = new Array:1=(' arr ')2=('kim')3=('jim')",
    "C": " var txt = new Array('arr ','kim','jim')",
    "D": "var txt = new Array='arr ','kim','jim'",
    "answer":"var txt = new Array('arr ','kim','jim')"
  },
 
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": " Which of the following is correct to write â€œHello Worldâ€ on the web page?",
    "A": "System.out.println(â€œHello Worldâ€)",
    "B": " print(â€œHello Worldâ€)",
    "C": "document.write(â€œHello Worldâ€) ",
    "D": "response.write(â€œHello Worldâ€)",
    "answer":"document.write(â€œHello Worldâ€)"
  },

  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which of the following is used to capture all click events in a window?",
    "A": "window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK);",
    "B": "window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );",
    "C": "window.handleEvents (Event.CLICK);",
    "D": "window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK );",
    "answer":"window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK)"
  },
   
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which of the ways below is incorrect of instantiating a date?",
    "A": "new Date(dateString)",
    "B": "new Date()",
    "C": "new Date(seconds)",
    "D": "new Date(year, month, day, hours, minutes, seconds, milliseconds)",
    "answer":"new Date(seconds)"
  },
  
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which of the following is a client-side Java Script object?",
    "A": "File",
    "B": "Function",
    "C": " FileUpload",
    "D": "Time",
    "answer":"File"
  }
]

